<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pages on Six Degrees of Ohio</title><link>http://localhost:1313/page/</link><description>Recent content in Pages on Six Degrees of Ohio</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About Us</title><link>http://localhost:1313/page/about-us/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/page/about-us/</guid><description>&lt;p>There is no us, there is just me, your faithful DJ, your old pal, Sergio.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I grew up listening to radio stations from all over the world on a homemade shortwave radio. I loved listening to people spinning playlists from the ether, and always felt like I was discovering things that had been unknown.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I dreamed about being that guy, sharing my record collection over the airwaves.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In an era where everything is available online, I am most content to know that I am sharing record finds with friends, both old and new. And that sharing happens on the air.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How to Submit</title><link>http://localhost:1313/page/how-to-submit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/page/how-to-submit/</guid><description>&lt;p>I have the opportunity to host a radio show on &lt;a href="https://wadsworthcommunityradio.com/">Wadsworth Community Radio&lt;/a> showcasing local music from or related to the Ohio area. It will be one hour each Saturday night at 8PM Ohio time.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I am looking for the following submissions:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Recordings of bands from or related to Ohio. Send finished/mastered recordings, no demos.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Recordings will be aired on FM radio, so they will be subject to FCC rules. This can be read “No cussing, or singing about things that would be otherwise banned.”&lt;/li>
&lt;li>You need not be actively playing out or recording.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Any genre is welcome, but I will be curating the shows so that they make sense and don’t confuse the listener.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h1 id="submission-guidelines">Submission Guidelines&lt;/h1>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>You are welcome to submit two high-quality (128k or better) mp3 to &lt;a href="mailto:sergio@sixdegreesofohio.com">sergio@sixdegreesofohio.com&lt;/a>. If you would rather submit physical media, contact me at the same address for the mailing address.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>When submitting a full album, please indicate which track(s) you would like to have considered for review.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Please submit full contact info: email address, web address, phone number, and any social media links.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>If you are actively playing out, please include a link to your tour dates.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>How to Tune In</title><link>http://localhost:1313/page/how-to-tune-in/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/page/how-to-tune-in/</guid><description>&lt;p>We air each Saturday night at 8PM Ohio time.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>If you are in the vicinity of Wadsworth, Ohio, you can tune in on 97.1 FM.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Anywhere else, you can tune in via the internet at:&lt;/p>
&lt;p>(&lt;a href="http://208.167.255.75:7259/live">http://stream.wadsworthcommunityradio.com:7259/live&lt;/a>)&lt;/p>
&lt;p>For the most up to date information on tuning in via the internet, you can find the full information &lt;a href="https://wadsworthcommunityradio.com/listen-live/">here&lt;/a>&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>